

ABHAY THORAT

FrontEnd Developer

An IT Engineer with an excellent technical background, good management skills as well as strong interpersonal skills. Project Experience and work experience UI Development being a Softawarre Developer wnated to pursuve career in UI and Software Development

Contact



+919309936070



linkedin.com/in/abhaythorat345b3317b



thoratabhay58@gmail.com



Pune, India

Education

BE (Information Technology)

2017-2021

Savitribai Phule Pune University Sanjivani College Of Engineering, Kopargaon

Skills

JavaScript Core Java

HTML5 Web API CSS3 NodeJS

Angular 2+ Versions SQL React JS GitHub

Certificates

JavaScript - The Complete Guide

Angular - The Complete Guide

Python for Data Science - NPTEL

Interests

Travelling And Exploring

Playing Cricket

Reading Books

Experience

Intern | Software Engineer Trainee

Quiesta Technologies, Pune Nov 2021 - June 2022

- Attended and participated in meetings and brainstorming sessions withteam members.
- Audited company's legal documents to verify compliant policies and procedures.
- Focusing on leaning programming Languages (Java, Html, JavaScript, SQL).

Software Engineer Trainee

Steepgraph System Pvt Ltd July 2022 - April 2023

- Working as Front End Developer.
- Working on Angular Library like Angular Materials, Prime Ng. Working on React JS Projects.
- Mostly Contributed myself in Ui Developement and API integration.

Projects

CareSource

- Client: United Health Group, United States
- Domain: HealthCare
- Roles And Responsibilities: Worked on Angular which combines web applications with Component based MVC capability to make development and testing of code efficient. Worked on Angular features like Two Way Binding, Custom Directives, Controllers, Filters, Services. Designed Custom Directives using Angular. Used Angular Directives like ngModel, ngFor, ngClass, ngIf, hidden, etc

Amazon web app clone using React.js

 this project is Amazon web app like application with functionality added such as Home Page, SignIn/SignUp with user authentication with google firebase, add to cart page, total amount, payment interface

Language

English Hindi Marathi